[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "911 OPERATOR: What's the problem?", "question_tokens": ["911", "OPERATOR", ":", "What", "'s", "the", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Two people aren't breathing.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "people", "are", "n't", "breathing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Ray"]}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "POS", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "CD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "911OPERATOR: A sweat lodge?", "question_tokens": ["911OPERATOR", ":", "A", "sweat", "lodge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "It was James Ray's version of a Native American sweat lodge ceremony where temperature's reportedly reached 120 degrees killing three of his followers and sending 19 to the hospital.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "James", "Ray", "'s", "version", "of", "a", "Native", "American", "sweat", "lodge", "ceremony", "where", "temperature", "'s", "reportedly", "reached", "120", "degrees", "killing", "three", "of", "his", "followers", "and", "sending", "19", "to", "the", "hospital", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "How are you in yourself and what do you feel about it all now that you served your punishment?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "in", "yourself", "and", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "all", "now", "that", "you", "served", "your", "punishment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I'm doing pretty well, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "doing", "pretty", "well", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What was going through your head when you heard guilty negligent homicide?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "your", "head", "when", "you", "heard", "guilty", "negligent", "homicide", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, if I can back up a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "I", "can", "back", "up", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And what was the reality, how was she when you were in prison?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "the", "reality", ",", "how", "was", "she", "when", "you", "were", "in", "prison", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "You know, it's interesting, Piers, that the first month that I was in and that was the better part of the first month.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "the", "first", "month", "that", "I", "was", "in", "and", "that", "was", "the", "better", "part", "of", "the", "first", "month", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "When you look back on it, what is the single biggest regret about any aspect of the preparation, the planning, any of the things that led to these people dying?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", ",", "what", "is", "the", "single", "biggest", "regret", "about", "any", "aspect", "of", "the", "preparation", ",", "the", "planning", ",", "any", "of", "the", "things", "that", "led", "to", "these", "people", "dying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "You know, hindsight is 20/20 and there's a lot of things that I wish were different.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "hindsight", "is", "20/20", "and", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "that", "I", "wish", "were", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "How does that happen in such an environment?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "happen", "in", "such", "an", "environment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "They sweat, right?", "question_tokens": ["They", "sweat", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "So what kind of barriers or controls that you have in practice given that it was clearly, potentially dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "kind", "of", "barriers", "or", "controls", "that", "you", "have", "in", "practice", "given", "that", "it", "was", "clearly", ",", "potentially", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, obviously not good enough, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", "not", "good", "enough", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Was there a heat limit that you used to have for the sweat lodge?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "heat", "limit", "that", "you", "used", "to", "have", "for", "the", "sweat", "lodge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, you really don't know how hot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "hot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Why was there no regulation?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "there", "no", "regulation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "There's no regulation for a lodge.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "regulation", "for", "a", "lodge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Again, why didn't you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Again", ",", "why", "did", "n't", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, I didn't know nor did anyone know that anyone was in a death -- in a life or death situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "nor", "did", "anyone", "know", "that", "anyone", "was", "in", "a", "death", "--", "in", "a", "life", "or", "death", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "You?", "question_tokens": ["You", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP"], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well I was in the lodge running the lodge which the prayers and the affirmations and all those types of things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "was", "in", "the", "lodge", "running", "the", "lodge", "which", "the", "prayers", "and", "the", "affirmations", "and", "all", "those", "types", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "And if is so why?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "is", "so", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I don't recall that at all, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "recall", "that", "at", "all", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Did you recall anybody saying to you, \"I've got to be out of here\"?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "recall", "anybody", "saying", "to", "you", ",", "``", "I", "'ve", "got", "to", "be", "out", "of", "here", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "RB", "''", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I do and I recall people leaving.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "and", "I", "recall", "people", "leaving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Were they panicky?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "they", "panicky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "AMES RAY: Some people wanted to quickly exit and one of the things I told them in the set up was to go our clockwise carefully because obviously there's a pit of hot rocks in the center.", "answer_tokens": ["AMES", "RAY", ":", "Some", "people", "wanted", "to", "quickly", "exit", "and", "one", "of", "the", "things", "I", "told", "them", "in", "the", "set", "up", "was", "to", "go", "our", "clockwise", "carefully", "because", "obviously", "there", "'s", "a", "pit", "of", "hot", "rocks", "in", "the", "center", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What was the system in place for that kind of eventuality?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "system", "in", "place", "for", "that", "kind", "of", "eventuality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "There were people positioned within the lodged that were supposed to take care of the participants.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "were", "people", "positioned", "within", "the", "lodged", "that", "were", "supposed", "to", "take", "care", "of", "the", "participants", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "911 OPERATOR: What's the problem?", "question_tokens": ["911", "OPERATOR", ":", "What", "'s", "the", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Two people aren't breathing.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "people", "are", "n't", "breathing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "''", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 258, "question": "911 OPERATOR: A sweat lodge?", "question_tokens": ["911", "OPERATOR", ":", "A", "sweat", "lodge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "He made one comment and they did say, \"She's passed out, she's passed out, I don't know if she's breathing\", and he said \"The door has now closed and this round has begun, we'll deal with that at the end of this round.\"", "answer_tokens": ["He", "made", "one", "comment", "and", "they", "did", "say", ",", "``", "She", "'s", "passed", "out", ",", "she", "'s", "passed", "out", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "she", "'s", "breathing", "''", ",", "and", "he", "said", "``", "The", "door", "has", "now", "closed", "and", "this", "round", "has", "begun", ",", "we", "'ll", "deal", "with", "that", "at", "the", "end", "of", "this", "round", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What do say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "I understand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "understand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Did you make yourself subliminally cut corners?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "make", "yourself", "subliminally", "cut", "corners", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I don't know, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "When you were told that people have died, three people have died, what was your immediate reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "told", "that", "people", "have", "died", ",", "three", "people", "have", "died", ",", "what", "was", "your", "immediate", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Shocked, denial, disbelief I couldn't comprehend it, anguish.", "answer_tokens": ["Shocked", ",", "denial", ",", "disbelief", "I", "could", "n't", "comprehend", "it", ",", "anguish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Do you fell guilty for what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fell", "guilty", "for", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "It was my event.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "my", "event", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "That there was an allegation that you left the scene pretty quickly, and just disappeared, is that true, and if so why did you leave so fast?", "question_tokens": ["That", "there", "was", "an", "allegation", "that", "you", "left", "the", "scene", "pretty", "quickly", ",", "and", "just", "disappeared", ",", "is", "that", "true", ",", "and", "if", "so", "why", "did", "you", "leave", "so", "fast", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "You know, Piers I wish I could say that I was enlightened enough to not have any impulse for self-preservation, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", "I", "wish", "I", "could", "say", "that", "I", "was", "enlightened", "enough", "to", "not", "have", "any", "impulse", "for", "self-preservation", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Did you look back at yourself with a certain degree of disgust perhaps at your actions and recognize that there was a character trait in you that you had to change?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "look", "back", "at", "yourself", "with", "a", "certain", "degree", "of", "disgust", "perhaps", "at", "your", "actions", "and", "recognize", "that", "there", "was", "a", "character", "trait", "in", "you", "that", "you", "had", "to", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "There was definitely character traits in me that hadn't changed and there's still are.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "definitely", "character", "traits", "in", "me", "that", "had", "n't", "changed", "and", "there", "'s", "still", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "And when you find yourself on those first few weeks as you've said on with death row inmates is about as low as your life could possibly have gotten coming from down this huge high, what the hell were you thinking as you've said in yourself?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "you", "find", "yourself", "on", "those", "first", "few", "weeks", "as", "you", "'ve", "said", "on", "with", "death", "row", "inmates", "is", "about", "as", "low", "as", "your", "life", "could", "possibly", "have", "gotten", "coming", "from", "down", "this", "huge", "high", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "were", "you", "thinking", "as", "you", "'ve", "said", "in", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I had to play mental games with myself because I had to wear shackles to the shower.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "to", "play", "mental", "games", "with", "myself", "because", "I", "had", "to", "wear", "shackles", "to", "the", "shower", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Humiliating?", "question_tokens": ["Humiliating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, humbling.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "humbling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "What would you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "First of all again, I'd say I'm sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", "again", ",", "I", "'d", "say", "I", "'m", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "... stuff, you thought about that?", "question_tokens": ["...", "stuff", ",", "you", "thought", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Did you lose everything financially?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "lose", "everything", "financially", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "ORGAN: How much did you have before all this?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "How", "much", "did", "you", "have", "before", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Millions.", "answer_tokens": ["Millions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "10, 20 million?", "question_tokens": ["10", ",", "20", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "You know it's a lot of my money was tied up in my business and in hard assets.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "my", "money", "was", "tied", "up", "in", "my", "business", "and", "in", "hard", "assets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "But do you think looking back it was an appropriate punishment given that three people had paid money to be in your tutelage lost their lives?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "looking", "back", "it", "was", "an", "appropriate", "punishment", "given", "that", "three", "people", "had", "paid", "money", "to", "be", "in", "your", "tutelage", "lost", "their", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I have no complaints.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "complaints", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "And this lady that you came with tonight?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "lady", "that", "you", "came", "with", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "She's in that category, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "in", "that", "category", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "I mean, now to see you were talking very emotionally about her at the start of the interview, when you came out what did she say to you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "now", "to", "see", "you", "were", "talking", "very", "emotionally", "about", "her", "at", "the", "start", "of", "the", "interview", ",", "when", "you", "came", "out", "what", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "AY: My mom is my greatest supporter.", "answer_tokens": ["AY", ":", "My", "mom", "is", "my", "greatest", "supporter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131125pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Samantha, first thing's first, do you ever have doubts about dating the George Zimmerman?", "question_tokens": ["Samantha", ",", "first", "thing", "'s", "first", ",", "do", "you", "ever", "have", "doubts", "about", "dating", "the", "George", "Zimmerman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Yeah, of course Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "of", "course", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}]